https://animal-world.com/privacy_policy.htm

Animal Stories - See Morehave bunches of this great plant. grows prolifically not for sale in ohio pet stores,
as it is considered an invasive species let me know if you want/need some   merrilee edison
Buying / Sellinghave bunches of this great plant. grows prolifically not for sale in ohio pet stores,
as it is considered an invasive species let me know if you want/need some merrilee edisonI have a male and female eastern gray squirrel for a new home. I prefer rehoming them together not as a pair. They are hand tamed and hand raised from birth. Email: northernharvest44@gmail.comMuller ReneePlease Help, I am looking to buy a leaf muntjac deer, and am willing to travel where ever to purchase one. Could you please email me your information, and some of your own personal opinions about them and how you would prefer for them to be taken care of (preference in diet, living area, etc.) my email is sammie007@hughes.net Thank you SammiesammieI'm looking for a male Himalayan Rabbit with black earsJoseph DavidI will like too buy two squirrel's a red on and a gray one my gmail is wbrandi629@gmail.com Is $200 a Nuff if not gmail me wbrandi629@gmail.com okBrandi WilliamsAny one having 100+ Gecko or 25+ Black Scorpion in Quetta can Contact me for Best Rates with Guarantee, We Offer Highest Rates . (QUETTA ONLY)KhanMore Classifieds
Animal-World > Privacy Policy
Animal-World Privacy Policy
About Us
This is a privacy policy for Animal-World. Our homepage on the Web is located at
http://Animal-World.com. The full text of our privacy policy is available on the Web at
http://Animal-World.com/privacy_policy.htm Users may go to
for information on how to opt-in or opt-out of use of their information.
We invite you to contact us if you have questions about this policy. You may contact us by mail at the following address:
Animal-World
217 So. Gateway
Ridgecrest, CA 93555
US
You may contact us by e-mail at
drjungle@verizon.net. You may call us at 760-375-3125.
Dispute Resolution and Privacy Seals
We have no privacy seals or other assurance mechanisms.
Additional Information
This policy is valid for 1 day from the time that it is loaded by a client.
Data Collection
P3P policies declare the data they collect in groups (also referred to as "statements"). This policy contains 3 data groups. The data practices of each group will be explained separately.
Group "Basic information"
We collect the following information:
Click-stream data
HTTP protocol elements
Search terms
This data will be used for the following purposes:
Completion and support of the current activity.
Web site and system administration.
Research and development.
This data will be used by ourselves and our agents.
The following explanation is provided for why this data is collected:
Data collected from all Web users: access logs, and search strings (if entered).
Group "Cookies"
At the user's option, we will collect the following data:
HTTP cookies
This data will be used for the following purposes:
Anonymous user analysis.
Anonymous user profiling and decision-making.
This data will be used by ourselves and our agents.
The data in this group has been marked as non-identifiable. This means that there is no reasonable way for the site to identify the individual person this data was collected from.
The following explanation is provided for why this data is collected:
Cookies are used to uniquely track visitors as they add or remove items from an Amazon.com shopping cart. The information only tracks unique visitors as they navigate the Amazon store.
Group "Mailing registration"
At the user's option, we will collect the following data:
Physical contact information
Online contact information
Given Name (First Name)
Family Name (Last Name)
This data will be used for the following purposes:
Completion and support of the current activity.
Contacting visitors for marketing of services or products. The user
must opt-in to this usage.
This data will be used by ourselves and our agents.
The following explanation is provided for why this data is collected:
This information is collected as an opt-in membership to our newsletter. Members will receive periodic newsletters from Animal-World. Membership can be cancelled at any time simply by sending an email with "Remove" in the subject line.
Cookies
Cookies are a technology which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a Web site. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it.
Our site makes use of cookies. Cookies are used for the following purposes:
Pseudononymous analysis
Pseudonym-based decision-making
Compact Policy Summary
The compact policy which corresponds to this policy is:
CP="IDC CURa ADMa DEVa PSAa PSDa CONi OUR NOR IND PHY ONL UNI COM NAV INT"
The following table explains the meaning of each field in the compact policy.
Field
Meaning
CP=
This is the compact policy header; it indicates that what follows is a P3P compact policy.
IDC
Access is available to contact information.
CURa
The data is used for completion of the current activity.
ADMa
The data is used for site administration.
DEVa
The data is used for research and development.
PSAa
The data is used for pseudononymous analysis.
PSDa
The data is used for pseudononymous decision-making.
CONi
The data is used for contacting the user, if the user selects it.
OUR
The data is given to ourselves and our agents.
NOR
The data is not kept beyond the current transaction.
IND
The data will be kept indefinitely.
PHY
Physical contact information is collected.
ONL
Online contact information is collected.
UNI
Unique identifiers are collected.
COM
Computer information is collected.
NAV
Navigation and clickstream data is collected.
INT
Interactive data is collected.
The compact policy is sent by the Web server along with the cookies it describes. For more information, see the P3P deployment guide at http://www.w3.org/TR/p3pdeployment.
Policy Evaluation
Microsoft Internet Explorer 6 will evaluate this policy's compact policy whenever it is used with a cookie. The actions IE will take depend on what privacy level the user has selected in their browser (Low, Medium, Medium High, or High; the default is Medium. In addition, IE will examine whether the cookie's policy is considered satisfactory or unsatisfactory, whether the cookie is a session cookie or a persistent cookie, and whether the cookie is used in a first-party or third-party context. This section will attempt to evaluate this policy's compact policy against Microsoft's stated behavior for IE6.
Note: this evaluation is currently experimental and should not be considered a substitute for testing with a real Web browser.
Satisfactory policy: this compact policy is considered satisfactory according to the rules defined by Internet Explorer 6. IE6 will accept cookies accompanied by this policy under the High, Medium High, Medium, Low, and Accept All Cookies settings.
Site Map
Pet Care Sheets
Team Members
Blog / Newsletter
Animal-World References
About Animal-World
Contact Info - Privacy Policy
